Confessions
Light!
月、第二のキラから、
またさくらテレビ宛にメッセージが届いた
The second Kira has sent Sakura TV another message for Kira.
This time they've sent a video and a diary.
今度はビデオと日記だ、
I thought that I'd better let you know...
一応、お前にも伝えておく
A diary?
日記？馬鹿がまた動いたのか
I bet that idiot's gone and done something stupid again.
Can't they just sit still and wait?!
じっとして待てないのか…
They're saying to show the diary on TV?
日記をテレビに映せって？
Yes, this is it.
ああ、これだ
May 2006
1st: Even though I said I wasn't going to attend the circle activities
____with GW High, my friends still rang and asked me to go.
4th: Went to see "Morning Musume" with my friend at the Saitama Super Arena.
5th: Last day of the holiday, but I just lazed around at home.
7th: School started, but I'd divided the notebooks for different classes
____with my friends, so I didn't attend.
10th: Got invited to a party by friends but turned it down. Yokohama is too far.
13th: A friend came to borrow a CD that I'd promised to lend them.
2006? Last year's diary, huh?
2006年、去年の日記か…
16th: Forgot about a report that was due.
_____Asked a friend to come over in order to copy theirs.
19th: Read "Jump" for the first time in ages.
_____Reading it all in one go was fun.
2006? Last year's diary, huh?
22nd: Met up with a friend in Aoyama. Looked at each other's notebooks.
Look at the entry under the 30th.
30日のところを見てください
28th: Apparently they are going to release the PZ3, which will be more amazing than the PZ2. One to watch!
30th: Confirmed that there was a Shinigami present at the Giant's match in the Tokyo Dome.
Confirmed that there was a Shinigami present in the Tokyo Dome.
東京ドームで死神を確認する。
I can only imagine that they're suggesting that we do this on the 30th of May.
5月30日にそうしようと言ってるようにしか見えない
If this goes out on TV, even the public will realize their intentions...
こんなのをテレビに映したら、
一般人にも意図してることがバレる…
In any case, the only way you can see a Shinigami is if you touch their Death Note.
大体、
ノートに触れなければ死神は見えないのに、どうやって…
In any case, the only way you can see a Shinigami is if you touch their Death Note.
How do they--?
22nd: ____Met up with a friend in Aoyama. Looked at each other's notebooks.
Hey, Rem?
ねえ、レム
Huh?
ん？
Even though I have the eyes of a Shinigami, I'm unable to see my own lifespan. Can you explain why that is again?
何で死神の目を持ってても自分の寿命は見えないのか、
Amane Misa
Even though I have the eyes of a Shinigami, I'm unable to see my own lifespan. Can you explain why that is again?
もう一度よく教えて
Humans possessing a Death Note need only see the lifespans of the humans they are going to kill.
ノートを持った人間は、殺す人間の寿命だけが見えればいい
Shinigami are unable to see each other's lifespans, and the same principle applies to humans who have Death Notes.
そして死神同士が、相手の寿命を見られないのと同様、
ノートを持った人間同士も、寿命は見えない
ふ～ん
22nd of May... at Aoyama, we looked at each other's notebooks.
5月22日、青山でノートを見せ合う
If by "notebooks", they mean "Death Notes", then... that's something that only I, as Kira, would understand.
ノートという言葉がデスノートであるとすれば…
キラである僕にしか伝わらない
The police should be focusing on the entry for the 30th of May...
それに警察は、まず5月30日の
"Confirmed that there was a Shinigami present at the Giant's match in the Tokyo Dome".
「東京ドームの巨人戦にて、死神の確認する」の方に注目する
I'm probably correct in assuming that the entry regarding Aoyama is the real message.
青山の方が本当のメッセージと考えて、ほぼ間違いないと思う
But in that case...
しかしこれでは…
What do you make of it, Light-kun?
どう思います？月君
I'd better be careful not to say anything careless here...
ここは下手な事は言わず、奴の出方を見た方がいい
It's best that I let him go first.
Right now, it just looks pretty stupid to me.
今のところ、馬鹿だとしか言いようがないな
Yeah! It's obvious that they're attempting to meet up with Kira at the Giants's game.
ですよね、巨人戦でキラに会おうというのは見え見えだし
Broadcasting this will cause a panic, and the game will be cancelled... don't they even realize this?
こんな物を放映したらパニックになり、
試合が中止になるのも分らないってことか…
If I'm honest... this is so dumb, I'm not quite sure how to deal with it.
正直、馬鹿っぽいだけに、
どう対処すればいいのが分らなくなりました
If we broadcast this diary, we'd also have to make the announcement that the match on the 30th will be cancelled.
日記を放映すれば、
30日の試合は中止という発表もしなければなりません
If we broadcast this diary, we'd also have to make the announcement that the match on the 30th will be cancelled.
Yet, if we don't broadcast the diary, the second Kira won't make their move.
日記を放映しなければ第二のキラは動かない
Plus, if we cancel the game, they may get angry, and who knows what they'll do...
それに、中止した場合怒って何をするか…
It'll be okay. The second Kira appears to worship Kira.
それは大丈夫ですよ
第二のキラはキラを崇拝しているようですし、
We should be fine in believing their promise to our fake Kira that they won't take innocent lives.
我々の作ったキラに余計な犠牲は出さないと誓ったことを、
信じていいでしょう
Anyhow, first of all, we need to broadcast this diary and announce that the game is cancelled.
とりあえず日記を放映し、試合中止を発表すると共に、
Then we'll announce that on the 30th, all the roads surrounding the Tokyo Dome will be controlled by us.
30日、
東京ドーム周辺の道路を封鎖し、検問をすると流しましょう
Then we'll announce that on the 30th, all the roads surrounding the Tokyo Dome will be controlled by us.
Lastly, we'll send a reply from our fake Kira, agreeing to the meeting.
その上で、また我々の作ったキラから
「了解した、会おう」という内容の返事をする
Lastly, we'll send a reply from our fake Kira, agreeing to the meeting.
Don't tell me... you think that they'll show up, despite how tightly the security around that area will be monitored?
まさか、ドーム周辺を検問しても来ると…考えているのか
I doubt that the real Kira will show, but I don't know about the second Kira...
キラの方は来ると思ってませんが、第二のキラは分りません
We don't know how stupid they really are... or even if they truly are as stupid as they seem.
どこまで馬鹿なのか見えませんから、
それと、そこまで馬鹿じゃないと言うことも考え、
We don't know how stupid they really are... or even if they truly are as stupid as they seem.
I'll try and see if I can figure out any other hidden messages.
この日記に他のメッセージが隠されていないか、考えてみます
If they're using a code that only those with a Shinigami's power would understand, then I won't be able to break it.
ちから
もし死神という能力を持った者同士にしか
分らない暗号が隠されていたら、
私には解読できません
But... we'll need to ensure that we keep a close surveillance on all of the locations that are mentioned.
だが、この日記に記されている場所は、
徹底的にマークしておくべきです
But... we'll need to ensure that we keep a close surveillance on all of the locations that are mentioned.
The 22nd; met up with a friend in Aoyama.
「22日　友人と青山で待合せ」
「24日　友人と渋谷で待合せ」
The 24th; met up with a friend in Shibuya.
Realistically, we can't expect any results, but we'll need to pay attention to anyone that's in Aoyama with a notebook, and anyone shopping clothes in Shibuya.
現状では無駄を覚悟で、青山ではノートを持つ者に、
渋谷では洋品店に注意を向けるしかありません
Just as I thought.
思っていた通り、もし偽キラが捕まった場合、
If the second Kira is caught, then I have to ensure that I get their notebook at the very least,
ノートだけでも僕が押さえなければ…
and in the worst case scenario, kill them and anyone else that's there.
最悪そこにいた者を含め、殺すしかない
I'll arrange to increase the number of surveillance cameras around Shibuya and Aoyama as much as possible.
この青山．渋谷には、今からできる限りの監視カメラを増設し、
In addition, on the respective days, we'll need to have as many plainclothes policemen as possible at each location.
当日はできる限り、私服警官を配備してもらいます
Well, I'll go, since I'll easily be able to blend in with the crowd at Aoyama and Shibuya.
じゃあ、青山．渋谷の街に似合いそうな僕が行きますよ
I'll go as well.
僕も行くよ
月…
Light!
It'll be okay, father.
大丈夫だよ、父さん
I occasionally go to Aoyama and Shibuya.
青山．渋谷は、たまに行ってる所だし、
Besides, I'm the least likely to look out of place wandering around there with Matsui-san.
松井さんと一緒にウロウロしてでも、
一番不自然じゃないのは僕だ
Moreover, the only person the second Kira is interested in, is Kira.
大体、第二のキラが興味あるのは、キラだけだ
Well, Matsui-san, let's leave the plans for Aoyama and Shibuya until tomorrow.
じゃあ松井さん、青山と渋谷のことは、また明日にでも
Okay, got that. Light-kun, take care.
わかった、月君
気をつけて
As soon as I get back outside and switch my phone back on, this always happens...
外に出て電源を入れるとすぐこれだ…
Yes?
はい
This is Ryuuzaki.
竜崎です
当日は月君のことも注意深く観察してください
I need you to observe Light-kun carefully during those two days as well.
This is confidential, so please keep this to yourself.
これを内密にお願いします
あ…はい、わかりました
Yes... I understand.
"As long as my suspicions aren't at 0%, be suspicious of his every move"... is that what he's saying?
ゼロパーセントじゃない限りは、
あくまでも疑っていろということか…
I'm home.
ただいま
Light! You're home late.
月、遅かったのね
Yeah.
ああ
They told me to keep my assistance with the investigation a secret...
捜査協力していることは秘密にするんだったな…
I've got a girlfriend at the university now.
大学で、ガールフレンドができたから
Oh!
あら
What?! Onii-chan's got a girlfriend?!
きゃっ！なに
お兄ちゃん彼女？すご
Incredible!
Hey, hey, I'm an 18 year old university student; it's only natural, right?
おいおい、僕も十八の大学生、そのくらい当たり前だろ
Sayu, you've got to try harder too.
粧裕もがんばれよ
Eh?! I-I don't want to try hard!
えっ？そ、そんなのがんばらないもん
Light? What about dinner?
月、夕飯は？
I had room service at the hotel, so I'm fine.
ホテルのルームサービスですませた
Onii-chan! What do you mean by "hotel"?!
ぎゃあー、お兄ちゃんホテルって
What? What? What kind of scandal have I unearthed?!
なになになに？問題発言～ ＞＿＜
So, Ryuk... there's something I want to ask you.
さてリューク、聞きたいことがある
Ah, I thought so.
あっ、やっぱり
If you're able to answer, please do.
答えられるなら答えてくれ
Are Shinigami on Earth allowed to talk to one another?
人間界で死神同士が会ったら、声を掛けたりしていいのか？
Not too sure.
どうだろう
I think that from the moment I possessed a human, it became against the rules for me to do that kind of thing without the human's permission,
オレは人間に憑いた時点で、憑いた人間の許可なく
そういうことするのはルール違反だと思うが
but there isn't really a law against talking, so the other Shinigami may come and talk to me.
別にそんな掟はないから、
相手の死神は、話しかけてくるかもな
So, you mean that there's a possibility that when the second Kira's Shinigami sees you, they'd be allowed to tell them that I am Kira?
じゃあ偽キラのほうの死神は、リュークを見たら、
僕がキラだと教える可能性もあるってことか…
Normally, they wouldn't. It depends on their personality.
普通はしないはずだが、性格次第だ
So, is is safe for me to assume that your personality is what I believe it to be?
で、リュークの性格は、
僕の考えてる通りでいいんだな
So, is is safe for me to assume that your personality is what I believe it to be?
Yup. If I saw a human with a Shinigami, I wouldn't tell you.
ああ、オレは死神の憑いてる人間を見ても、ライトには教えない
Well, I think that's the right choice, Ryuk.
ま、リュークが正しいと思うよ
Thanks.
どうも
Huh? The fake Kira's already thought it through this far?!
ん？
偽キラ…ここまで考えているのか
What is it?
どうした？
Aoyama is a huge place. I was doing some research on how to go about looking for them, and I found this...
青山と言っても広い、
どうやってお互いを見つけ出すのかと思って、
調べてみたんだが…
On the 22nd, there's an event at the "Note Blue" nightclub.
NOTE BLUE
22日、青山のノートブルーというクラブでイベントがある
Aoyama...
Aoyama literally translates to "Blue Mountain"
青山、ブルー、それにノート…
"Blue"...
and "Note"...
え、結構手がこんでるな
Seems that they've put a bit of effort into this.
It's possible that they're smarter than I thought.
思ってたより知恵があるのかも…
Although if that's true, I may have to be more careful.
だとすれば、それだけこっちも気をつけなくてはいけないが、
Right now, it seems that going to this "Note Blue" might be worth a shot.
NOTE BLUE
現状ではこの、ノートブルーに賭けてみる価値はある
But you don't want them to find out that you're Kira, do you?
しかし、
あっちには自分がキラであること、知られたくないんだろ？
あ、あの…月君
Err... Light-kun...
What's this?
これは一体…
These are my friends at the university.
僕の大学の友達です
Nice to meet you.
どうも…
This is my cousin, Tarou-san.
僕の従兄の太郎さん
It's his first time in Tokyo, and he says he wants to have fun somewhere like Aoyama or Roppongi.
東京は初めてで、
青山とか六本木とかで、楽しく過ごしてみたいんだって
So, let's do our best for him.
みんなよろしく
He's also looking for a girlfriend, any applicants?
ああっあと、
彼女も募集中だそうなので、誰か立候補してくれない？
Hey, Light-kun!
おい月君…
Just what I expected from Light-kun!
さすが月君
No one would think that there are police present in this group of young people.
この若者の集団に、刑事がいるなんて、まず誰も考えない
If I move around in a group, even if Ryuk gets seen, they won't know who he's possessed.
これだけの人数で動けば、もしリュークを見られても、
誰に憑いているかは分らない
If I move around in a group, even if Ryuk gets seen, they won't know who he's possessed.
In addition, it'll act as a wall against L's surveillance cameras.
L の観る監視カメラへの壁にもなるし、
It's not bad for investigative purposes either.
捜査方法としても悪くない
All that remains is to watch the entrance of "Note Blue" prior to, and after the performance.
NOTE BLUE
あとは開演前後の、ノートブルーの入口を見ればいいだけ…
Found you!
み～っけ
Yagami... Tsuki-kun, is it?
つき
夜神…月君、かな
Yagami... Tsuki-kun, is it?
月 = "Tsuki" (moon). Read as Light in this case, but this is not shown by the written form.
You're the only person whose lifespan I can't see!
一人だけ寿命見えてないよ
That settles it! He's Kira!
キラ決定
I didn't think that it'd be this easy to meet you!
こんな簡単に会えるなんて、思ってはなかったよ
Hey, Rem, let's go home.
さあレム、帰ろう
えっ？せっかく会えたのに、もういいのか
Huh, already? After all the effort you've put into meeting him?
It'd be bad for me to go up to him with all these people around and say something like, "I'm so happy to meet you, Kira-san!", wouldn't it?
人がいっぱいいる前で、
「キラさん、お会えできて嬉しいです～」
なんて挨拶したら悪じゃない
Now that I know his name, it'll be easy to find out more.
名前わかったし、あとは簡単に調べられるわよ
It's an unusual name, after all.
変わった名前だしね
Oooh! So it's written "Tsuki" but pronounced as "Light"!
Blood type:
Weight:
Height:
D.O.B.: _____February 28th, 1989
月と書いて、「ライト」と読むのか
Oooh! So it's written "Tsuki" but pronounced as "Light"!
That's kinda beautiful!
なんか素敵
それにしてもすごいな～夜神月
Still, he's pretty amazing, isn't he, this Yagami Light...
Apparently, while he was in his second and third year at Junior High, he was the National Tennis Champion!
中学二年．三年と、テニスの全国大会で優勝
Also, for Toudai University's Entrance Ceremony this year, he gave the speech as the freshers' representative!
今年は東応大学の入学式で、新入生代表の挨拶
There's no photo, but it can't be anyone else with a name like this.
写真はないけど、こんな名前他にいるわけ無いし
I'd never guessed that Kira would be so young and handsome...
まさかキラがあんな若くてカッコイイなんて…
Everything is far better than I'd imagined it would be!
何もかも想像以上
There are places unashamedly selling registers, too.
平気で名簿売ってるところあるし、
This world is such a twisted place.
世の中狂ってるね
住所もわかっちゃた
Now I know his address too!
In the end, on both the 22nd in Aoyama and the 24th in Shibuya, there was no evidence of any suspicious activity occurring.
結局今のところ、
22日青山、24日渋谷
どちらも何も起きた形跡はなし
あとはもう30日のドームしか…
All that remains now is the Dome on the 30th.
There was no one suspicious at "Note Blue" either...
NOTE BLUE
ノートブルーにも、それらしき者は一人も現れなかった
Don't tell me that it's really going to happen at the Dome?
まさか本当にドームで…
Ryuuzaki! Sakura TV have received another message from the second Kira.
竜崎、さくらテレビ宛に、
第二のキラからのメッセージが来ました
消印は、23日です
It's postmarked the 23rd.
キラを見つけることができました
I was able to find Kira.
テレビ局の皆さん、警察の皆さん、
To everyone at the TV station and the police force, thank you.
ありがとうございました
I-Impossible?! Where? At Aoyama?
ま、まさか…
どこで…青山か
I-Impossible?! Where? At Aoyama?
Did their Shinigami see Ryuk and tell them that?
相手の死神が、リュークを見つけて教えたのか
No... In the crowd, it should have been impossible to tell who Ryuk was possessing...
いや、誰に憑いていたかは判断できないはず
I took every precaution to ensure that I wasn't followed...
尾行にも細心の注意を払った…
If this really is connected to the diary... and was really posted on the 23rd... the only date it leaves is the 22nd, in Aoyama, as a corresponding date.
もしこれが本当なら、23日に投函されていることから、
該当するのは22日の青山だけ…
If this really is connected to the diary... and was really posted on the 23rd... the only date it leaves is the 22nd, in Aoyama, as a corresponding date.
The only people to have gone from headquarters were Matsuda and Yagami Light.
この本部から青山に行ったのは、松田と夜神月のみ
So, is Yagami Light Kira, after all?
やはり夜神月がキラか…
Yet there's absolutely no proof that it happened in Aoyama...
しかし青山という確証はない
This is bad, they've found them.
「見つけた」って、まずいぞ
うん…キラと第二のキラが手を組んだっということに…
Does this mean that Kira and the second Kira have joined forces...?
まだ手を組んだとは言い切れません
No, we don't know for sure that they've joined forces yet.
The second Kira only said that they'd "found" Kira.
第二のキラは「見つけた」と言っているだけです
They may yet have to make contact.
接触は、まだかもしれない
Now that we've progressed this far, the only thing that we can do is have the police appeal to the second Kira.
ここまで来てしまったら、
第二のキラに今度は警察が呼びかけてみるしかありませんね
Appeal to?
呼びかける？
Yes. The police will need to offer the second Kira a favorable deal if they tell us who Kira is.
はい、第二のキラに警察側から好条件を出し、
キラが誰なのかを教えるよう、呼びかけるんです
へへっ、最悪の展開じゃないのか、これ
Things can't get any worse for you, can they?
This isn't good... I have absolutely no idea how this second Kira may react...
まずいな…相手があの偽キラだけにどう動くか…
Yet, there's no way that I can stop them...
しかし、呼びかけを止める手立てもない
If Kira doesn't already know who you are, it's not too late.
もし、またあなたが誰なのか
キラにわかっていないのなら間に合います
You mustn't approach Kira purely for the fun of it.
興味本位でキラに近づいては絶対にいけない
If you come in contact with Kira, you will almost certainly die.
キラに接触すれば、あなたは必ず殺されます
You'll only be used!
利用されるだけです
とうと
今あなたにできることは、人の命の尊さをよく考え
All you should do now, is to think carefully about the value of human life.
Give us all the information you have on Kira, and atone for your crimes.
キラの情報を我々に教えることで、罪を償い、
Save the people of the world from the fear of Kira.
キラの恐怖から世界の人々を救うことです
どこ行くんだ？
Where are you going?
To confess.
名乗り出る
Oh, so this is the choice you've made...
あぁ…こっちか
I wonder if that's Dad...
あら、お父さんかしら
はい
Coming!
おっかえり
Welcome home!
Eh?
あれ…？
Good evening. My name is Amane Misa.
こんばんは、弥海砂と申します
I've come to return an important notebook that Light-san left behind at university.
月さんが大学に忘れた、大事なノートを届けに…
ちょ…ちょっと待てて下さい
P-Please wait for a moment.
Onii-chan!!
お兄ちゃん～！
Notebook?!
ノート…！まさか…
Don't tell me?!
Pleased to meet you. I'm Amane Misa.
あ、初めまして、弥海砂です
I was watching the TV, and I thought that you might worry about me, so I just had to come here.
テレビ見てたら心配してるんじゃないかと思って、
どうしても我慢できなくなって…
This notebook...
このノートを…
っ…デスノート
Death Note?!
A Shinigami!
死神…
It's the fake Kira...
偽キラだ
Come in.
上がっていけよ
Oh, are you sure that it's okay? I'm so happy.
え、いいんですか、嬉しい…
Mother, she's gone through all the effort of bringing this over, so could we get some tea or something?
母さん、わざわざ届けてくれたんだ、お茶か何か
Yes, yes of course.
そう、そうね…
I've told you about this before.
こないだ言ったろ
Take a seat.
座って
あ、ありがとう…
Thank you.
How did you know?
何故わかった
Ah, you really haven't traded your eyes, have you?
あ、やっぱり、目の取引はしてないんですね
If you trade your eyes with a Shinigami, you're able to see people's names and lifespans,
死神の目を持つと、人間の寿命と名前を見ることができる
but you're unable to see the lifespan of someone who has a Death Note.
でも、ノートを持ってる人間の寿命が見えないんです
Oh, I-I didn't know that much about it...
いや…そこまで詳しく知らなかったし、オレ…
Okay, I've understood that much, but if you'd been caught, Kira's secrets would've been revealed.
まぁ、それはわかったが、
君がもし警察に捕まっていたら、キラの秘密がバレていた
大丈夫、私は捕まってないし、
It's okay. So far, I haven't been caught, and if I do as you say from now on, I won't get caught.
これからはあなたの言うとおりに動けば捕まらない
I'm right, aren't I?
そうでしょう？
And then I'll see L's name.
そして私が L を名前を見る
I'll be your eyes...
私はあなたの目になる
so...
だから…
So?
だから？
Please make me your girlfriend!
彼女にして下さい！
な…
彼女…
G-Girlfriend?
Yes!
はい！
If I handle this the wrong way, I could end up dead, but...
こいつを下手に扱うと殺される可能性がある、しかし…
Impossible.
無理だ
That day in Aoyama, there were triple the usual number of surveillance cameras operating.
大体あの日の青山は、いつもの三倍の監視カメラが付いていた
If you went to Aoyama that day, you would have been captured on tape somewhere.
あの日青山に行ったのなら、必ず君はどこかに映っている
I'll be there as well.
僕もだ
If we were to become close after that...
その二人がその後接近したら、
今ここでこうしてる事すらまずいんだ
Even meeting each other now is risky.
それくらいわかってくれ
At least try to understand that.
These are photos of me on the day I went to Aoyama.
これ、青山に行った日の、私の写真です
There's no doubt that she's unrecognizable.
これなら確かにわからないな
So, what about fingerprints?
じゃあ指紋は？
All those things you sent to the TV station were covered in the same fingerprints.
キミがテレビ局に送ったものには、全て同じ指紋が付いている
But those aren't my fingerprints!
あれは私の指紋じゃない
私だって、少しは考えて行動してます
Even I think through things a little before I act!
Until recently, I was living in Kansai, and I had a friend there who was interested in the occult.
最近まで私は関西にいて、オカルド好きな友たちがいたんです
私がつくったインチキな心霊影像を、
色んなテレビ番組に送ろうって持ちかけたら、
I made a fake video containing footage of spirits and approached her about sending it to some TV stations.
彼女は乗ってきた
She was really into the idea, and I got her to dub ten copies.
ビデオテープ十本にダビングさせ、私の指紋がつかないよう
Then I copied the "Kira" over to them, without getting my own prints on them, and added the audio.
そのビデオテープの上から、あのキラの影像を重ね撮りして、
音を入れたんです
So, what's your friend doing now?
その友たちは、今どうしている…
If you told me to kill them, I'd do it right now!
あなたが殺せというなら、今すぐにでも殺します！
If you still refuse to trust me, you can look after this notebook.
どうしても信じられないなら、
このノート、あなたが預かってください！
As long as you only look after it, I'll still be the owner, so I should still be able to use the power of my eyes.
預かるだけなら、所有権は私にあるから、
目の能力は持続する
そうよね、レム
Right, Rem?
That's true.
確かに
This way, I won't be able to kill you, but if I become useless to you, you can kill me.
これなら私はあなたを殺せないし、
私が不要になったら、あなたが私を殺せばいい
Why is she willing to go this far...
何でこいつここまで…
But you could already have torn out a page of the Death Note and hidden it somewhere.
しかしもうノートから何ページが切り取って、
隠し持っているかもしれないじゃないか
Why do you have to be so suspicious of me?!
何でそこまで疑うの？
I don't mind if I really am just used by you!
私は、あなたに利用されるだけでもいいの、信じて…
Please, believe me...
How can she say such things?
何故そこまで言えるんだ
A year ago, my parents were murdered right in front of me by a burglar.
私の両親は、ちょうど一年前…私の目の前で強盗に殺された…
I couldn't forgive that... yet the trial dragged on and on. Eventually they judged that he'd been falsely accused..
絶対に許せなかった
でも裁判は長引き、そのうち冤罪の見方まで…
I couldn't forgive that... yet the trial dragged on and on. Eventually they judged that he'd been falsely accused..
そんな時、その犯人を裁いてくれたのはキラ…
But then... Kira passed judgment on him.
To me, Kira is an absolute being!
私にとってキラは、絶対的な存在…
No matter... no matter what, I wanted to meet you!
どうしても、どうしてもあなたに会いたかった…
I wanted to say thank you.
お礼を…言いたかった…
You went through all this trouble for the sole purpose of meeting Kira?
今までの無理なやり方は、「キラに会いたい」という一心ゆえ
She was able to implement the bare minimum of countermeasures against surveillance cameras and leaving fingerprints...
一応、監視カメラ、指紋への対策など、最低限はできている
She's not as stupid as I thought...
思ったより馬鹿ではない
Plus, she's saying that she'll do as I say from now on...
それに、これからは僕に従うと言っている…
I understand...
わかった
I can't be your boyfriend, but I can pretend to be one.
彼氏にはなれないが、振りはしてあげられる
Those eyes of yours, which you traded half your remaining life for in order to find and aid me, will be a great weapon.
僕に会うため、僕の力になるために、
残りの寿命を半分にした君の目は、武器になる
ありがとう…
Thank you. I'll try my hardest to make you love me.
好きになってもらえれるよう、頑張る…
To be continued